magicsw.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy

﻿ 

## Magic EdTech - Privacy Policy

Magic EdTech respects and understands the importance of your privacy – and are therefore committed to affording complete protection to the personal information of our customers who use our products and services or visitors of our website, and of the learners whose information we may have access to and when you apply on our website for an open position. It is in recognition of this need for security, our commitment to EU GDPR and Secured management of any information received /collected by us that Magic EdTech has established this Privacy Policy.

This privacy policy is applicable to our websites – www.magicedtech.com and and to our products, including the MagicBoxTM and Appitest platform, and any services we provide. It also applies to our marketing practices. We ensure total transparency in all our dealings.

Data Privacy is important to us and we strive to be transparent in our data collection and use practices

## **What information is collected?**

####  1\. Personal information collected on our website

As a general practice, no personal Information is collected about a visitor to the website, apart from the personal information submitted by the visitor himself/herself in a ‘contact us’ form or ‘submit resume’ link. We shall use such Personal Information for the purpose you share it with us. However, at times, certain information may be collected from you when you visit the website. Such information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the website, pages viewed etc. This gives us an idea of which parts of our website users are visiting, in order that we may improve the content to offer you better services. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

#### 2\. ID, Customer information for support and maintenance

When you register to use a Magic EdTech product, create an ID with us or use our services for development or support we collect information that is unique to you and identifies you. This may include your name, email address, phone number or payment information all in accordance with applicable law. Some information is required and other information is optional. Sometimes information regarding eligibility may be required. At times we may rely on information from public sources.

#### 3\. Information collected while using our online products and applications especially during activation and automatic updates

When our product/application is used information may be collected on how it is used. We may collect information (like an IP address, or the type of device used) that your browser or device typically sends to our servers whenever you use our website, product or application. We may use information that led you to our website – for example the search terms used or the device being used - through cookies and similar technologies. Often this information is anonymous and if associated with you kept strictly confidential. If you do not want us to collect this information, you can tell us by opting out or by either declining or customising cookie settings on our website

#### 4\. Magic EdTech emails

We do contact organisation or executives as a part of our marketing campaigns. We do so, as we believe we have legitimate interest to promote our products and services andit also benefits our prospects. We do not do any mass mailing and carefully reach out to selected professional with a personalised approach. The emails we send you as part of our marketing campaigns allow us to know if you have received or opened the email, or clicked a link within the email. If you do not want us to collect this information from marketing emails, you can opt out of receiving such emails by clicking on the unsubscribe button.

#### 5\. Buttons or tools on our websites related to other companies and social media pages

Our websites may include buttons or tools that link to other companies’ services (for example, a Facebook or Google button). We may collect information about your use of these features. In addition, when you see or interact with these buttons, tools, or content, or view a Magic EdTech web page containing them, some information from your browser may automatically be sent to the other company. Please read that company’s privacy policy for more information, as these sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any linked Web sites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of the sites or for the privacy practices of those other Web sites.

We may collect information when you interact with our social networking pages or use the sign-on features.

#### 6\. Hosted services provided by Magic EdTech

We provide hosted services to many companies that may sometimes require the collection of information through cookies and other technology to collect analytic data required by the product and to understand our users and their likely interests. No information is collected without consent.

## **Where do we store this data?**

Information and data files are stored on our servers and the servers of companies we hire to provide services to us. We do not share, sell or lease any kind of information collected to any third parties for their marketing uses.

## **How do we use the information collected?**

We use this information to:

  * To fulfil our contractual commitment and to enhance the performance of our contract with you.
  * Allow you use of our products and applications and respond to your requests
  * Provide you with the services, support or information requested and monitor effectiveness
  * Improve our website’s user experience and communicate better to engage users
  * Enhance the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. To send marketing emails or messages related to our products and services
  * Monitor aggregate metrics to conduct our market research and understand our customers better
  * To process your job application for an open position.
  * Analyze, diagnose and fix issues in our product and service offerings.

In all cases this information is not shared with any third party. It is used by Magic EdTech as above or to prevent/respond to protection of our websites or applications. In some cases like with hosted services, we may share information with those that provide us with technology services (e.g. web hosting and analytics services), but strictly for the purpose of carrying out our work. All such vendors used by us are EU GDPR compliant and have siged a Data protection agreement with Magic to secure your data. We may be required to share information with law enforcement or other third parties when compelled to do so by court order or other legal process, to comply with statutes or regulations.

If we merge with or are acquired by another company, and if all of our assets are acquired by another company, this information will most likely be one of the assets to be transferred. However, we will not transfer any personal information of our customers until absolutely necessary to provide you with a continuity of service and only when the new owner maintains and provides the same level of data privacy standards as we do. In such cases, we will provide you with notice and an opportunity to opt-out of the transfer of identifiable data.

##  **How do we secure information collected?**

We understand that the security of your information is vital and have in place strong administrative, technical, and physical security controls and measures to keep data safe and secure. Our privacy practices are designed to provide protection for your personal information, all over the world.

To protect information stored in our servers, through Amazon Web Service infrastructure at various locations like the US, Australia and India, access is limited (through user/password credentials and two factor authentication) to those employees who require it to perform their job functions. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to safeguard the account registration process and sign-up information. Other security safeguards include but are not limited to multifactor authentication, data encryption, firewalls, and physical access controls to building and files.

We would like to caution our visitors about phishing attacks, wherein unscrupulous third parties seek to extract sensitive and confidential information from you by posing as a genuine website or by sending an email misrepresenting it to be from a genuine source. Please be aware that we never seek sensitive or confidential information such as regarding your financial or health record through emails or through our websites. If you receive such a message claiming to be from Magic EdTech, then please do not reply to it and immediately bring it to our attention by contacting the Webmaster.

Magic EdTech also recognizes the receipt, transmission or distribution of spam emails (unsolicited bulk emails) as a major concern and has taken reasonable measures, to minimize the transmission and effect of spam emails in its computing environment.

##  **Can this information be reviewed?**

In some cases and at our discretion this information may be accessed by respective organizations to correct any mistake in that information, and to delete any information we no longer have business reasons for retaining. You can do this by sending us an email. Magic EdTech strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy and information, no matter where that information is collected, transferred, or retained. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, we intend to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if information is transferred from your country to other countries that may not require an adequate level of protection for your information.

##  **Rights over your personal data**

Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:

  * Be informed about the processing of your personal data (i.e. for what purposes, what types, to what recipients it is disclosed, storage periods, any third party sources from which it was obtained, confirmation of whether we undertake automated decision-making, including profiling, and the logic, significance and envisaged consequences).
  * Object to your personal data being processed for a particular purpose or to request that we stop using your information.
  * Request not to be subject to a decision based on automated processing and to have safeguards put in place if you are being profiled based on your personal data.
  * Ask us to transfer a copy of your personal data to you or to another service provider or third party where technically feasible and otherwise required by applicable regulations.
  * Withdraw, at any time, any consent that you have previously given to us for our use of your personal data.
  * Ask us to stop or start sending you marketing messages at any time.
  * Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a "data subject access request"). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
  * Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected. It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your working relationship with us.
  * Request the erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where you think that we do not have the right to process it.
  * Any request for access to or a copy of your personal data must be in writing and we will endeavour to respond within a reasonable period and in any event within one month in compliance with Data Protection Legislation. We will provide this information free of charge unless the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. We will comply with our legal obligations as regards any individual’s rights as a data subject.

If you would like to contact us in relation to any of the rights set out above please contact us by email dpo@magicedtech.com.To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before providing you with the details.

##  **RIGHT TO COMPLAIN TO THE ICO**

You can contact the ICO if you have any concerns about how Magic Ed techhas handled your personal data and you also have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues. You can contact the ICO via their helpline on 0303 123 1113. You can find out more information about your rights as a data subjects, their regulatory powers and actions they can take on their website <https://ico.org.uk/>

##  **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of the information we collect and how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Where links are provided to other websites it should be noted that they are not and cannot be governed by our Privacy Statement. We cannot guarantee your privacy when you access other websites through any link provided on this website.

## Magic Minds

At Magic, we endeavor to maintain an environment of trust, openness and respect for the individual. Here are some comments from fellow Magicians. 

  1.   2.   3.   4. 

#### "Sumanta Mishra"

"At Magic the learning never stops. The culture and team at Magic always helps to translate that learning into action and achieve new milestone."

#### "Rishi Raj"

"Magic respects opinion of every employee wherein they has a voice that is heard and respected. Each employee are provided a space to work to their potential and are empowered to build on their strengths."

#### "Sonia Gupta"

"Magic strongly believes leadership is an action, not a position, and stands for the equality of its women employees."

#### " Kuljeet Singh"

"It is a great learning experience each day with new domains and technological platforms to work with. An incubator for freshers that provides best of industry experience and a rewarding working environment." 

#### "Rohit Kumar"

"We can learn programming anywhere, they tought us how to write program but In Magic, Programming is not about writing its all about Thinking"

#### "Achal Jain"

"Magic has nice work culture. People are easily accessible and you get opportunities to learn and experiment with best technologies."

#### "Ankana Mukherjee"

"An open work culture and a great place to learn about technology for newcomers."

#### "Sharmistha Ghosh"

" In Magic, there are no female leaders, there are just leaders. Believers in gender equality."

#### "Tarun Singh"

"Words can neither qualify nor quantify how much I'm enjoying working with Magic. A great place to work with the excellent working environment and good learning opportunities."

#### " Neha Singh"

"Magic makes each and every employee feel valued, and invests in each individual's growth and success. Coworkers work well together, trust each other to do a good job, and enjoy spending time together outside of work also" 

#### "Anchala Kumari"

"Magic makes each and every employee feel valued, and we love it! They show genuine and authentic appreciation for the work we do and the effort we put in."

Noida

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience : 5 -7 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1** **Desired Skills**

  * Previous working experience as a Product Owner for 1-2 years
  * In-depth knowledge of Agile process and principles
  * Take the lead of scrum teams as the Product Owner
  * Plan and prioritize product feature backlog and development for the product
  * Ensure that the team always has an adequate amount of prior prepared user stories to work on
  * Providing vision and direction to the Agile development team
  * Assess value, develop cases, and prioritize stories, and epics to ensure work is aligned with product strategy
  * Work closely with Product Management to create and maintain a product backlog according to business value
  * Lead the planning product release plans and set the expectation for delivery of new functionalities

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience : 5 -7 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1** **Desired Skills**

  * Proven exposure of generating potential leads from assigned geography (Preferably Europe/USA/AMEA)
  * Should have exposure into B2B sales
  * Good experience in Customer Research/Industry Research practices
  * Product, e-learning background- Preferred
  * Proficient with corporate productivity and web presentation tools
  * Ability to multi-task, prioritize, and manage time effectively
  * Research accounts, identify key players and generate interest
  *  Must have worked on- Salesforce/Hubspot tool
  * Individual contributor as well as a good team player

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience : 3 - 6 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1** **Desired Skills**

  * Should have expertise in the Spanish Language.
  * Able to speak fluently in the Spanish language.visualization and writing documents/Proposals/Bid formsand approach notes.
  * Acts as SPOC for the HMH Leads for work planning and changes
  * Triage, verification with the customer over the calls.
  * Attends weekly status calls
  * Gains detailed knowledge of the applications in order to provide support to the Spanish test engineers on the team
  * Has the ability to support the activities of the test engineers
  * Interacting with JIRA and Tracking of SLA’s

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience : 5-7 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1** **Desired Skills**

  * Presales with technical content writing experience with rich domain expertise in publishing
  * Should have versatile global delivery experience in leading requirements gathering & analysis, solution visualization and writing documents/Proposals/Bid formsand approach notes.
  *  Understanding RFPs and POC scope / requirements
  *  RFI / RFP / Bid Forms Responses,
  * Understand offerings, competition, Client business needs
  * Excellent written and verbal English
  * Good Analytical skills.

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience :5 - 6 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1** **Desired Skills**

  * Test exp in API testing using jmeter or anyother tool.
  * Should have experience in selenium, junit, testing
  *  He should have experience of testing platforms
  *  Should know how to design automation test cases
  * Should know testing fundamentals.
  * Strong in written & verbal communication (Must Have)
  * Should have experience in working in scrum environment.

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : Finserv** **Experience :3 - 6 Years** **Resources Reqd : 2  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Design, develop Python/Shell script to manage AWS Infrastructure used for Blockchain based application
  * Propose new enhancement & new tools/technologies to improve any existing product/process/framework etc
  * Solid knowledge of Python and Shell Scripting
  * Basic understanding of AWS, Docker, CI/CD tools like Jenkins
  * Automation of CI/CD integration with Python clients/shell
  * Solid knowledge of Python and Shell Scripting
  * Knowledge of blockchain concepts especially with Ethereum Platform
  * Knowledge of ELK, Splunk, Grafana, Prometheus

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : Finserv** **Experience :3 - 5 Years** **Resources Reqd : 2  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Work with functional teams to analyze and identify automation test cases, identify test data requirement for automation
  * Interact with application teams and functional testers to discuss automation scope, framework tailoring
  *  Should have knowledge of different types of frameworks used in Selenium
  * Should have experience in Page Object Model Set-up and Implementation
  * Should have knowledge of HTML5, DOM Structures and XML
  * Experience in Automated Testing with Selenium and strong working knowledge of Selenium Webdriver using C#
  * Experience in API and WebServices testing (e.g. Postman, SOAP UI) and understanding of data formats like JSON and XML
  * Have implemented automated tests within Agile teams ideally within continuous integration.

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience :4+ Years** **Resources Reqd : 1  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Strong design fundamentals User centric design focus with ability/knack to perform and drive contextual inquiry
  * Practice concepts of rapid prototyping in day to day interaction with stakeholders
  * Ability to work independently in a larger cross-functional team, with demonstrated ownership of user experience design
  * Team player with excellent communication
  * High level of negotiation and presentation skills with customer and other internal/external stakeholders.
  * Prepared to travel to client locations for project related conversations.
  * Keen observer of trends, styles and technologies; introduce new approaches to evolve solutions and processes
  * Lead ideation processes and storyboarding; prepare and present concepts and solutions to stakeholders, customer.
  * Design for latest digital technologies, platforms and devices.

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience :7+ Years** **Resources Reqd : 1  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Strong design fundamentals User centric design focus with ability/knack to perform and drive contextual inquiry
  * Practice concepts of rapid prototyping in day to day interaction with stakeholders
  * Ability to work independently in a larger cross-functional team, with demonstrated ownership of user experience design
  * Team player with excellent communication
  * High level of negotiation and presentation skills with customer and other internal/external stakeholders.
  * Prepared to travel to client locations for project related conversations.
  * Keen observer of trends, styles and technologies; introduce new approaches to evolve solutions and processes
  * Lead ideation processes and storyboarding; prepare and present concepts and solutions to stakeholders, customer.
  * Design for latest digital technologies, platforms and devices.

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience :3 - 5 Years** **Resources Reqd : 1  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Strong on Reactjs, web pack, Redux
  * Able to competently complete development activities using the React JavaScript Library
  * JavaScript/Jquery/CSS/HTML5
  * Strong knowledge of OOJS
  * Working knowledge of Responsive application design.
  * Ability to stand alone development of modules.
  * Knowledge of versioning tool Git

**Job Location: INDIA** **Business Division : EdTech** **Experience : 4 - 6 Years  ** **Resources Reqd : 2  ** **Desired Skills**

  * Hands-on programming skills to produce high-quality code with least bugs on deployment
  * Spring Boot,Spring Data,Spring Security,Spring Session
  * Ability to do Object-Oriented design and programming.
  * Ability to use Java & Spring design patterns.
  * Ability to do database tables or collections or documents schema design for at least one
  * each from given SQL and NoSQL databases: SQLDatabases - Oracle / MySQL / PostgreSQL
  * Good understanding of Code Quality and Code Review processes of an Agile Process
  * Public Cloud Service Provider like AWS, Google, Microsoft etc.

**Experience:  2-6 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Strong on Reactjs, web pack, Redux,
  * JavaScript/Java/Jquery/CSS/HTML5

  * Able to competently complete development activities using the React JavaScript Library And Apollo GraphOL.

**Experience:  1-7 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Strong design fundamentals. User centric design focus with ability/knack to perform
  * and drive contextual inquiry - persona building, data analysis
  * Practice concepts of rapid prototyping in day to day interaction with stakeholders
  * Keen observer of trends, styles and technologies; introduce new approaches to
  * evolve solutions and processes
  * Self-motivated - ability to work independently in a larger cross-functional team, with

  * demonstrated ownership of user experience design
  * Team player with excellent communication. High level of negotiation and
  * Presentation skills with customer and other internal/external stakeholders. Prepared to travel to client locations for project related conversations.

**Experience: 6-10 Years**

**Employment Mode: FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Good experience in Vendor Management, Vendor Sourcing, Negotiation.
  * She/he will be responsible to identify the pool of available vendors and getting the work done in minimum time with maximum quality
  * Expected to create and maintain a large database of vendors who can work in Creative Arts, DLOs, E-learning projects from PAN India level as and when required.

**Experience:  5-8 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Solid foundation in data structures, algorithms, OO Design and patterns, Distributed Computing, Probability and Statistics, Applied Math + Algorithms.

  * Experience in Implementing a chatbots for any industry. Also have experience in development of chat bots or other AI, machine learning or NLP technologies.
  * Learn about advanced signal processing techniques. Processing natural language labels to extract indicators
  * Visualising indicators in an offline dashboard designed for mobile interface
  * You can program Java or a similar object-oriented language. Experience with one or more languages such as JavaScript, Java, jQuery, Node.js, Python, C++, R language.
  * Experience with web application frameworks like Spring, Spring Boot.
  * Experience in artificial intelligence, machine learning technology
  * Familiarity with database (SQL, Oracle, Stored Procedures, MongoDB) and can work with relational as well as non-relational databases
  * You have deployed apps to cloud services like AWS. Experience with Amazon Lex,Alex, Elasticsearch.
  * Experience building large/medium-scale distributed systems using RESTful web services. You have experience working with third party APIs
  * You have experience with graphics tools like Tableau or Kibana

**Experience:  6-8 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Strong proficiency with JavaScript
  * Strong proficiency with Node.js and libraries available for it
  * Strong understanding of asynchronous programming and the nuances that go with it.
  * Strong understanding of design principles behind a scalable application
  * Experience implementing unit tests for JavaScript
  * Experience with moving and transforming data
  * Experience with Azure Cloud and Logic Apps a strong plus

**Experience:  1-5 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Strong design fundamentals. User centric design focus with ability/knack to perform

  * and drive contextual inquiry - persona building, data analysis

  * Practice concepts of rapid prototyping in day to day interaction with stakeholders

  * Keen observer of trends, styles and technologies; introduce new approaches to

  * evolve solutions and processes

  * Self motivated - ability to work independently in a larger cross-functional team, with

  * demonstrated ownership of user experience design

  * Team player with excellent communication. High level of negotiation and

  * presentation skills with customer and other internal/external stakeholders. Prepared to travel to client locations for project related conversations.

**Experience:  2 – 5 Years**

**Mode: FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Strong understanding in Angular, JavaScript,
  * Strong understanding in HTML and CSS
  * Familiarity with cross browser and different environment compatibility
  * Strong computer science fundamentals and deep understanding of web technologies

  * Should able to write jQuery widgets.

**Experience:  6-8 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Should have strong understanding of JavaScript programming, Angular
  * Must be aware of React.js, Typescript, build optimization, Grunt, Gulp
  * Managing a team of engineers
  * Above average into HTML & CSS
  * Must be from programming background

**Experience:  6-8 Years  
Employment Mode: FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Good understanding with testing methodologies

  * Test strategy, planning, execution, tracking, and reporting

  * Manage the test resources at Project level

  * GO / NO GO Decision making

  * People management with teams of more than 3 people

  * At least 1 year as Test Lead

**Experience:  1-2 Years**

**Employment Mode:  FTE**

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Knowledge of manual testing

  * Able to understand the project requirement closely and testing process, also come up with any gap wherever applicable.

  * Able to find all the valid issues in the application. Should have worked on Functional and Content Projects

  * Takes quality responsibility for the task performed by an individual.

  * Open to work on multiple projects as per the requirements and help others meeting the critical timelines

  * Able to raise queries.

**Experience:** 4-8 Years  
**Employment Mode:** FTE

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

  * Should be an advanced Java Professional with 4+ years of experience in Spring and Hibernate.
  * Database – Experience working with ORM frameworks like Hibernate/JPA and MyBatis
  * Should be eligible in Java based platform’s optimization, performance tweaks and code reviews
  * Strong Logical and Analytical Skills + Strong Problem Solving & Troubleshooting Skills
  * Ability to grasp concepts & ideas quickly, & learn new skills fast. Quick learner

NYC

The Director (Business Development & Sales) will represent the Digital Learning Products division of Magic Edtech in north America and identify prospects in the market, build suitable partnerships, identify alternate segments and areas where these products can be sold and generate sustainable revenue and margins for the business. Visit 

 to know more about our products – MagicBox, MagicSync, and LE-AP. ****Experience Range****

  * 8+ years

**** **** ****Location****

  * New York

****Role/Job Description****

  * Primary responsibility is generating revenue; product sales; SaaS platform License sales/contracts.
  * Generate leads thru networking and other channels like Events/Conferences
  * Demonstrate the SaaS product and also present the product and capabilities.
  * Networking in the relevant industry using online channels like Linked In and offline channels

****Qualifications/Experience/Background****

  * Exposure in managing Institutional/corporate (B2B) sales in either Education or corporate training is a must
  * Functional Knowledge of technology to be able to answer basic questions about the product
  * Rolodex, past experience of generating leads/sales in Professionals Services/ Learning and Education businesses.
  * Experience in selling SaaS/Cloud/Product sales, License contracts, Implementation / Professional Services and solutions,
  * Hands on Experience to price a solution, write proposals, doing presentations and negotiations.

****Role – Sales - Magic Software**** Candidates having experience in technology services sales in EdTech, Publishing, Digital Learning, Technology and Services business are ideal candidates. ****Experience Range****

  * Entry Level: under 5-7 years

**** **** ****Location****

  * NYC, NY

****Role/Job Description****

  * Primary responsibility to bring leads, and generate revenue
  * Sales, Cold calling, Email Campaigns
  * Networking
  * Attending events

****Qualifications/Experience/Background****

  * Basic understanding of the EdTech Business – ideally in Digital Learning, Content, and Technology.
  * Functional Knowledge of digital content publishing, content delivery, learning analytics and cloud technologies
  * Rolodex, past experience of generating leads/sales in EdTech, Publishing, K12, Higher, Professionals Learning businesses.
  * Experience in selling services and solutions, making proposals, presentations and negotiations.

****Role – Sales - Magic Software**** We are looking for Sales Executives who can grow to take on an independent role in managing sales and building large account-based relationships within Publishing (Academic) segment. We’re offering full-time job opportunity where the candidates will be able to handle technology and content solutions sales into the identified accounts within publishing segment _This is an entry level position, so the candidates will be evaluated on their commitment to build a career in sales, business development, and account management._ This position is open to candidates who may have some sales experience in B2B enterprise sales, and basic understanding of consulting/solutions services. Ideal candidates would be those candidates who have experience in Learning / Content services sales in Publishing business. ****Experience Range****

  * Entry Level: under 2-6 years

****Location****

  * NYC, NY

****Role/Job Description****

  * Primary responsibility to bring leads, and generate revenue
  * Sales, Cold calling, Email Campaigns
  * Networking
  * Attending events

  Ideal candidate will have: 

  * Some Experience in Sales
  * Experience in selling services and solutions, making proposals, presentations and negotiations.
  * The following are additional desired requirements but not necessary: 
    * Basic understanding of the Publishing(academic) and Learning Business – especially in Digital Learning, Content, and Technology.
    * Functional Knowledge of digital content publishing, content delivery, learning analytics
    * Rolodex of names/decision makers in Publishing Houses who take outsourcing decisions and who are business leaders, Product Managers/Program Managers.
    * Experience of generating leads/sales from Publishing Houses – specifically those who deal with K12, Higher, Professionals Learning businesses within the publishing houses.

****Qualifications/Experience/Background****

  * Bachelor's degree
  * Competitive cumulative GPA. Additional requirements might apply.
  * Results oriented with demonstrated organizational and time management skills
  * Strong interpersonal skills to build rapport with prospective and existing customers
  * Global teams experience, multiple time zones, ability to work with other cultures.
  * Possess excellent analytical, written, and verbal communication skills
  * Ability to work semi-autonomously in a fast-paced environment
  * Extensive travel across USA/Euro/India

**Desired Skills:**

Magic Edtech provides technology and content services to Publishing and Edtech companies need help with learning content solutions, product engineering, application Support and QA Testing services for digital learning and Edtech platforms which leverage mobile, and cloud technologies and relies heavily on data analytics.

The Sr. Sales executive will run campaigns and identify prospects, build revenue and margins on a sustainable basis from the target clients in Publishing market segment.Please contact [SalesEdTech@magicsw.com](mailto:SalesEdTech@magicsw.com)

**Desired Skills:**

Magic Edtech provides technology and content services to Publishing and Edtech companies that need help with learning content solutions, product engineering, application Support and QA Testing services for digital learning and edtech platforms which leverage mobile, and cloud technologies and relies heavily on data analytics.

The Technology Consulting Solutions executive will provide thought leadership, technology solution design, and program management consulting services to Magic EdTech clients. Please contact [SalesEdTech@magicsw.com](mailto:SalesEdTech@magicsw.com)

**Desired Skills:**

Magic Edtech provides technology services to Edtech companies need help with product engineering, application Support and QA Testing services for edtech platforms which leverage mobile, and cloud technologies and relies heavily on data analytics.

The Sr. Sales executive will run campaigns and identify prospects, build revenue and margins on a sustainable basis from the target clients in EdTech market segment. Please contact [SalesEdTech@magicsw.com](mailto:SalesEdTech@magicsw.com)

**Experience:** 6-8 years  
**Location:** NYC/Virginia  
**Mode:** Permanent

**Key Skills:** Business Strategy, Solution Design, Technical Proposal Building, ​Project Management​ (SCRUM/ Agile Projects)​, ​Account & Engagement​ Management​, Business Analysis, Team Management, Research, Estimation, Fluent Communication

* * *

**Role Description:**

  * Experience in ​​ideating solutions for customers, designing technical proposals & solutions, building SoWs, Understanding client’s technology platforms and aid clients in transforming process and workflows
  * Exposure in managing projects in Education publishing​, HigherEd & EdTech​ segment
  * At least 6 years presence in the US and working experience with Education publishing​, ​HigherEd & EdTech​ segment consulting companies
  * Understand client business requirements around content technology, accessibility
  * Familiar with (A) Platform Engineering and Technology Project Management (B) Content​ Life cycle​ ​(​Design, Content Management, Content Authoring, Content Production, Content Testing, Content Distribution​)​.
  * Manage productivity and outcomes, with 100% team billing including self-utilization
  * Excellent communication skills 
  * Create a process and JIRA workflow for individual projects and assign priority to each
  * Define and Manage tickets in JIRA for each identified component
  * Work with offshore project manager to manage work progress, assign JIRA tickets to offshore, onshore teams
  * Review project progress with stakeholders and keep up to speed with schedule and budget

**Experience:** 6-8 years  
**Location:** SFO  
**Mode:** Contract  
**Engagement Duration:** 3 months

**Key Skills:** Project Management, Client engagement, Business Analysis, Team Management, Estimation, Communication

* * *

**Role Description:**

  * Exposure in managing projects in Education publishing segment
  * At least 6 years presence in the US and working experience with publishers/ed-tech consulting companies
  * Understand client business requirements around content technology, accessibility
  * Familiar with (A) Platform Engineering and Technology Project Management AND / OR (B) Content Design, Content Management, Content Authoring, Content Production, Content Testing, Content Distribution.
  * Manage productivity and outcomes, with 100% team billing including self-utilization
  * Excellent communication skills Create a process and JIRA workflow for individual projects and assign priority to each
  * Define and manage tickets in JIRA for each identified component
  * Work with offshore project manager to manage work progress, assign JIRA tickets to offshore, onshore teams
  * Review project progress with stakeholders and keep up to speed with schedule and budget

**Experience:** 5-7 Years  
**Mode:** FTE

* * *

**Desired Skills:**

Magic Software, New York is hiring a Sales Executive for its Digital Learning technology and services initiatives serving EdTech companies. This is an entry level position, work experience under 5-7 years. Please contact [SalesEdTech@magicsw.com](mailto:SalesEdTech@magicsw.com)

  * Basic understanding of the EdTech Business – especially in Digital Learning, Content, and Technology.
  * Functional Knowledge of digital content publishing, content delivery, learning analytics
  * Rolodex, past experience of generating leads/sales in EdTech, Publishing, K12, Higher, Professionals Learning businesses.
  * Experience in selling services and solutions, making proposals, presentations and negotiations.
